[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
What are you doing here?
Choi Jeong-yo.
Just give me another shot.
N N
The solo…
You've got to let me do it…
I'll never do that.
That piece was written
out of your hatred for me, wasn't it?
Do you really think…
that anyone else could play it but me?
I'd like… to thank you.
Because going through this, I realized my own limitations.
But…
when it comes to "Nemesis",
I'm the only one who can do it justice.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Huh?
Nemesis is my composition.
You're just a performer.
You're nothing more than a tool for me to use.
And it's up to me to choose which tool is best for the work.
It's not.
Nemesis was meant for me from the moment you wrote the first note.
I just need to master it.
Then the piece will finally be complete.
This is your chance to finish it.
Don't let revenge get in the way.
Cut the bullshit and get lost.
You don't have the right nor the skill to play it.
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
EPISODE 11
LETTER OF APPOINTMENT KANG JI-HYE
HYUN-SOO
Take your time. I've arrived.
INCOMING CALL HAN HYUN-JEONG
Hey, Ji-hye.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I'm fine.
I was so worried, you know.
You didn't pick up any of my calls.
What do you want?
Oh, um, I just wanted to talk.
It's about Pi-o's contract renewal.
Things aren't good at the company,
so I think we'll need to reconsider.
I'm going to need an explanation.
Ah, I'll just be honest with you, okay?
We took a huge financial hit when that album recording fell through.
Up until now, we just wrote it off as a rough patch.
But now that the album's fallen through too,
there's a lot of talk at the company.
So I don't think we can renew his contract.
It's better if you hear it from me than from Pi-o himself, right?
Han Hyun-jeong.
How could you do this to me now?
You saw it yourself.
Choi Jeong-yo did all of that on purpose to mess with Pi-o.
Oh, Ji-hye, I really don't know, you know?
Anyway, there's - no point in talking about it.
It'll just upset us both further.
Gosh, Honestly, I feel terrible that it's come to this.
Uh, my team will call Pi-o directly to go over the details,
so just a heads-up to let him know.
I'll call again, 'kay?
Mom, what was that call regarding?
Oh… You heard what I said, didn't you?
How could you even consider doing that?
You know the state of mind he's in, right now.
You want us to be the first to turn our backs on him?
If we refuse to renew his contract over this,
what artist is ever going to trust us enough to sign with us?
Isn't it our job as a management agency to stand by our artists?
You should stay out of this.
Something… feels off about them.
Remember? When Jeong-yo went missing?
There were whispers that Pi-o was somehow behind it.
Oh come on, you believe that?
There's no way Pi-o could've done a thing like that.
You may not know him as well as you think.
Where's your self-respect?
You followed him around like a lovesick puppy, and he dumped you anyway.
Ugh, I already hate his guts for breaking your heart like that!
Besides, with his questionable past and bleak future,
what is there left to defend?
I can't do it.
I won't do it.
Look, I know what you're going to say.
But if I turn myself in while Pi-o is in the state that he's in,
how will he…
get back on his feet?
Everyone's already cutting ties with him as it is.
If you terminate Pi-o's contract, I'm out.
I'll quit the company as well.
Consider that.
Oh my God, how can you how can you be such a fool!
Ji-hye.
The longer you put this off,
the harder it is to make it right.
You need to be strong, for everyone…
but especially…
do for your sake.
I know, I already know all that.
Give me a little more time.
Just wait a tiny bit longer.
CHOI JEONG-YO
We need to talk. I'll go to your office. Choi Jeong-yo,
So, what brings you by today?
Choi Jeong-yo,
be honest with me.
You're doing this to Pi-o on purpose.
What do you mean by that?
You're doing this
cos you heard that Pi-o might've been involved in your kidnapping.
If so, stop it right now. Cos it's not true.
Hmm…
How can you be so sure?
So I'm right.
That's why you did this.
Look.
Seriously.
I've known the two of you longer and better than anyone else.
Pi-o was the only one
who kept searching the world for you. Even after everyone else gave up,
he kept looking.
So how could you
let a rumor…
let you believe the worst about a good friend?
And isn't it possible that he wasn't actually searching for me,
but was trying to make sure I was dead instead?
Wow, Choi Jeong-yo.
I'm really disappointed in you.
When Pi-o heard that you were dead,
he was so shocked he couldn't get out of bed for days.
And I had to fly all the way to Moldova to get him.
You'd been missing for ten years, when he heard you were dead.
He couldn't even take a sip of water.
So how could you…
Forget it.
What more can I say to someone who's using their amnesia
as a way to hurt someone.
In any case,
if you keep going after Pi-o like this…
I won't just sit back and watch.
You've been warned.
Why don't you answer? When are we going public?
Just wait.
Put it on hold.
Music that moves people,
deeply in their hearts is music that carries a lifetime within it.
Your desire to make music even if you had only one day to live.
Your very life.
Put that into your music.
And right here!
I used marcato to capture the emotions of betrayal and revenge.
But…
do you actually think your performance is conveying all of those emotions?
No, not in the slightest!
Mister Kang.
I just wanted to remind you that we're meant to watch the violinist videos at
three o'clock. In the second-floor conference room.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, one thing…
my replacement as artistic director…
Put that on hold for now.
Yes, Of course.
Is there a reason?
Is… something bothering you?
There's a few things I'd like to check.
I'll need time.
Right.
How are preparations going for the premiere?
Yeah, well…
I might be worried over nothing,
but a conductor mustn't treat musicians as mere tools to be used…
The performance belongs to the musicians on stage, not the conductor.
Only when you realize that will you create great music.
I've been meaning to ask you something for a while.
Mister Kang…
Do you
believe that a morally flawed artist is fundamentally unworthy of creating art?
Or do you think art and the artist's private life should be
judged separately?
Can you clarify?
Well, art…
is supposed to be a reflection of the artist's life.
So if an artist commits a crime that is unforgivable…
should society still accept their work without any reservation?
I guess it's an age-old debate.
Are you trying to playact at being a judge, or are you in fact trying to
make some music here?
I do not think an
artist's sins will either pollute or corrupt the music that they create.
In fact, I believe that one must be intrinsically flawed to create great art.
What we should be wary of…
is using our art as an excuse to commit evil acts without remorse.
To punish and judge a flawed, imperfect artist is not our place at all.
Ultimately, an artist who has committed unforgivable sins
will face punishment for as long as the music they produced lives on.
Do you think an eternity of judgment…
Is a blessing or a curse?
I'm sorry.
I had to take an urgent call.
So… shall we go through the applications first before reviewing the clips?
Yes, let's do that.
Gosh, it's so hard to find the right person.
Even though they're all winners of prestigious competitions,
none of them quite fit the…
The tension you wanted…
IS that more like it?
N
ENSEMBLE ROOM
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry for letting myself in without your permission.
I knew you wouldn't change your mind unless you saw for yourself
how much my playing has changed.
This isn't going to change anything.
What'd ya think?
Did you not like my performance?
Just admit it already.
I'm the only one who can do this piece justice
You know that's the truth.
Oh…
So, I've had this feeling…
Uh…
You have another performer in mind to play your piece.
Isn't that right?
-Sorry? -I'm just speaking from experience.
Every premiere seems to have a performer who's destined to play it.
And…
something tells me it's not me.
And if that's really the case…
you should choose
the person you want.
-What are you-- -You're a composer.
You should do whatever it take for your piece to shine.
I'm just speaking from experience.
Every premiere seems to have a performer who's destined to play it.
Just admit it already.
I'm the only one who can do this piece justice.
You know that's the truth.
Hey Mister Choi…
Who the hell are you?
Uh well, I'm uh…
You don't need to ask that.
You know who I am, right?
What is it you want to say?
You don't have to pretend with me.
You see, I met Kang Pi-o's mom the other day.
And, uh… she seems to be all right.
I suppose you're looking for revenge…
Aren't ya?
Though, uh…
Ya can't be half-assed about it, if you really wanna get it.
If you're gonna take someone down, do it right and crush them completely!
Let everyone know you did.
They'll leave you alone.
Want my help?
You're still living like a dog, aren't ya?
Who said you could go after him?
No one touches him but me, is that clear?
If you dare to lay a finger on Kang Pi-o,
I'll make sure you don't breathe another day.
You got that?
Ouch…
You busted my wrist.
Hospital fee?
Dude…
I say "Kang Pio" and you go nuts.
You've gotten ruthless, man.
See ya around.
Good luck, punk.
N
Come outside.
I'm out front.
Do it. The show.
I don't want you to think this means I've forgiven you.
I'm just doing this…
because I need Nemesis to be played perfectly.
I know. I got really good seats!
Good evening, everyone. I'm Yoon Seon-ju,
president of the Hankook Symphony Orchestra.
Thank you all for joining us at this festival celebrating
the eightieth anniversary of…
the Hankook Symphony Orchestra…
I hope this will be an occasion we all remember for years to come.
And now, may the show begin.
Do you think I even care about your opinion?
Yeah. You will never beat me.
You chase after it, and there it is in the distance.
Chase after it again, and it's farther out of reach.
Even so, do you still want to take this windy, thorny path?
Say you had less than a month to live,
would you still want to keep playing the piano till the very end?
The piano is the one thing that brings me joy.
If I had one day left to live…
I would still want to play the piano.
Command the stage with your own energy.
If your energy is strong enough,
you can pull the entire orchestra and the conductor into your own world.
You were right all along.
This piece was meant for you and you alone.
I would like to sincerely thank you all for coming.
I'm truly grateful for your support.
It was an absolute honor
for me to perform Nemesis for you.
Conductor Choi Jeong-yo's masterpiece.
However…
I've come out on stage…
to make a confession tonight.
The truth is…
I don't deserve to be standing up here today.
Nine years ago…
You may recall a kidnapping at the Prague Harmonie Competition.
The one who ordered the kidnapping of Choi Jeong-yo back then…
was…
myself.
As a result,
I have enjoyed undeserved glory.
I've basked in it for nearly a decade.
I offer my sincerest apologies to Conductor Choi Jeong-yo.
He endured years of suffering cos of me.
As of this moment,
I intend to walk away from all the privileges I have been given
and accept the punishment I deserve.
To everyone who has supported me all these years…
I apologize to you.
I'm sorry for letting you all down.
Seriously? This is unbelievable.
Wait, what just happened?
Why you…
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry.
And thank you too.
It took me until today…
to truly understand you.
What the hell does that MEAN!??
Mister Kang Pi-o?
I'm Inspector Han Sang-gu
from the Major Crimes Investigation Unit.
We've some questions. Would you come with us please?
Uh,
Wait, I think there's been a misunderstanding.
Just wait a moment.
Hold on. Pi-o, tell me what's going on right now! Is it really true?
Pi-o! Pi-o, WAIT!
Just wait, please!
Let him explain!
Please wait Officers!
Who knew Kang Pi-o would be the one
-behind it all along? -Hey, so he really was arrested?
-Guess he really did it. -Guess he did.
-Kang Pi-o? Why? -Oh my gosh!
What's going on? Is that for real?
Quick look it up on your phone. Oh it is true!
KANG PI-O CONFESSES TO INVOLVEMENT IN CHOI JEONG-YO'S DISAPPEARANCE
-No he did, go on check another site, -I can't believe it! He couldn't have!
Check the news.
CALLING… KANG JI-HYE
Why isn't she picking up the phone?
Oh. Excuse me, Officer?
Where is the Pianist, Kang Pi-o, being held right now?
Oh, he's being interviewed.
So you can't see him.
Please let me see the detective in charge.
I'll explain everything.
I'm the one who did it.
It was all me you see?
My son is innocent, Officer.
I understand what you're saying, ma'am,
but he's being interviewed right now,
so you can't see him.
Please go home for now.
When they are finished… You can request to see him.
-But I did it. -Ah, sure.
I'm the one you should arrest! Detective!
Ms. Kang.
Jae-in.
What am I going to do?
You know, right?
You know the truth.
Pi-o didn't do it. I swear, he didn't!
It was all…
-It was… all me… -Oh!
Wanna grab a bite?
Oh, er, I'm sorry,
So we calling this a date, or…
but I can't let you meet with the suspect alone.
Call it whatever you want…
-It's not allowed. -No.
Please, I need to see him.
Um Just a moment. Wait here.
What are you doing?
You…
You ruined everything. You know that?
Do you have any idea what it took for me just to hold on all these years?
Do you…
Do you really think this is how I wanted it to end?
I was supposed to be the one to judge you, and if you died I was meant to
have killed you, so WHY!!!???
I'm sorry.
This was the best that I could do and you know it…
You're far too talented an artist to waste your time on this.
Your quest for revenge will destroy your soul.
Stop using your hate to make music…
and make it for yourself.
Okay, it's time to go Mister Choi!
-Who are you to tell me that? -Time to leave!
Calm down!
Who do you think you are lecturing me? Damn it!
-You need to leave, now! -Come on, let's step outside.
What gives you the right?!
INCOMING CALL HYUN-CHUL
Shit…
Where are you?
HYUN-CHUL WHERE R U?
MISSED CALL HYUN-CHUL
Did the police say anything to you?
It's not true.
There's been a mistake, hasn't there?
No, it's not true…
Pi-o didn't do it.
Then why would Pi-o say something like that?
Because I did it.
Just what are you saying?
Pi-o didn't do it.
Because I ordered the kidnapping.
You're saying it was you?
That's right.
That's what I said!
Pi-o was going to lose that day!
So I made sure he would win!
Are you…
Are you even human?
How could you do such a thing?
What kind of monster are you?
This whole mess is on you, you know that?
If you had given more affection to Pi-o, I never would have had to do that.
Dad, if you'd only accepted Pi-o as your grandson,
I never would have done something that crazy!
Why did you do that? Why did you do that to me?
Why did you do that to Pi-o?!
Why'd you do it!!? TELL ME
Why did you do that…
Why did you do that?
Why, Daddy?
Why did you do that?!
I…
came to turn myself in.
I was the one who did it.
My son knew nothing about it.
He found out the truth recently.
He's just trying to protect me…
That's why he's turned himself in.
You can check through Pi-o's phone.
There's a photo of me meeting with the kidnapper when I paid him to do it.
You should look for it.
I'm sorry, ma'am…
We checked Kang Pi-o's phone.
We didn't find anything like that.
-It was there… -Ma'am.
Mister Kang Pi-o, uh…
submitted conclusive evidence
that he has been in continuous contact with the criminals that were behind the
kidnapping. And recently,
He withdrew… a large sum of money in Moldova…
to hand over to the kidnappers.
Um…
I just want make one thing clear.
There is no way that you can take the blame for your son's crime.
So if you would- Please stop interfering…
and go home.
Believe me I swear, it was really me.
Oh… Please.
Please believe me!
I was behind it!
N N
Jeong-yo.
Will you forgive me?
I was the one who had you kidnapped.
Pi-o wasn't involved.
I don't know, I must have lost my mind back then.
I did such a disgusting thing to you.
Pi-o didn't know anything about it and he only recently found out the truth.
He wanted us to beg for your forgiveness.
But I refused, and threatened to kill myself.
That's why he didn't tell you.
Even still, Pi-o still calls me his mother…
And he has chosen to take the blame for everything that I've done.
Jeong-yo.
Could you testify to the police that…
Pio didn't do it.
That you remember that it was me that did it?
I deserve your hatred…
yet no matter how hard I try to think of another way
I can't think of anyone else to ask for
help but you, please help make this right.
Let me bear the punishment.
Please just save my son.
Do you actually expect me to believe that?
I understand that you want to protect your son,
but why would you come here and ask this of me?
Why would you ask the one whose life he ruined completely?
N
Please go home now, or I'll call the police.
No! No, wait
It's true. You have to believe me, Jeong-yo.
IT was all my fault.
It was all me. Pi-o,
Pi-o didn't know anyth-- No!
Jeong-yo! Jeong-yo! Jeong-yo!
Jeong-yo! Jeong-yo!
Jeong-yo, please listen to me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I did you so wrong.
Pi-o was your good friend.
You can hate me all you want, but please don't hate Pi-o.
Please…
During your one-on-one with the suspect,
you spoke to him
as though you already knew that he was guilty.
Was this actually the case?
Did you know that?
I'm sorry.
And thank you too.
It took me until today…
to truly understand you.
This was the best that I could do and you know it…
You're far too talented an artist to waste your time on this.
Your quest for revenge will destroy your soul.
Stop using your hate to make music…
and make it for yourself.
No.
I don't… remember.
All right then,
and everything you said?
What was all that?
About how Kang Pi-o ordered your kidnapping.
I just…
happened to hear a rumor about it.
Mister Choi.
Choi Jeong-yo?
Hello, Mister Choi.
I have something to tell you about Mister Kang Pi-o.
Could we talk for a moment?
Oh, you may not know who I am,
Mister Choi, but I feel like I've known you for so long.
I'm so happy to finally meet you in person.
What is it you wanted to tell me?
Well, you see…
The truth is…
Mister Kang did not arrange to have you kidnapped back then.
In fact, he desperately hoped you were still alive.
What are you talking about, Mister?
Did you know that Mister Kang had been
secretly searching for you for the last five years,?
And I was the one looking into it.
So what?
How can you be sure he wasn't
just checking to see if I was really dead or not, can you prove that?
Cos I saw how he reacted when he heard that you had passed away.
He was absolutely devastated.
Did Ms. Kang tell you to look for me?
Why the hell are you spinning such bullshit lies like that?
Do I really look that stupid to you that I'd buy into this cheap trick?
When we went to meet the gang,
I had my recorder running.
This contains Mister Kang's real feelings.
Why did you kill him?
Was it for money?
Did you abduct him for that reason? Or did someone--
Enough.
You want to know?
Three million lei. Then I'll tell you.
[Struggles
TELL ME!!!
Mister Kang, don't!
You killed him for something so small? You know who he was? He was my FRIEND!
Come on, stop!
Do you know who we are?
You little…
You know what?
Now, six million.
Then I'll tell you.
And I also got to see you pay off another one of them.
Is there an international bank close by here?
CHOI JEONG-YO
I'VE ALREADY MEMORIZED IT ALL USE IT IF YOU NEED IT!
Come back,
Jeong-yo.
Kang Pi-o,
come on out.
You may go home now.
What's the reason for releasing me?
Did my mother turn herself in, claiming that she was behind it?
Let me be very clear.
She must have somehow fabricated evidence to show that she did it,
but it's not true.
Don't believe her, because I did it. So please…
Um…
That's enough, Kang Pi-o.
We've reviewed all the evidence and that facts prove…
that you are not the culprit.
Besides that…
The victim has testified that you didn't do it.
Do you admit to arranging Mister Choi Jeong-yo's kidnapping?
Yes.
I admit to it.
When did you meet the kidnappers?
On March 18th, Two thousand seventeen…
As I recall, I met with them near Wenceslas Square in Prague.
SEOUL CENTRAL POLICE STATION
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Pi-o.
I had no idea what you were dealing with,
and I just kept blaming you.
Resenting you.
But still…
you should have told me.
You didn't have to carry it on your own.
I was there for you.
I'm sorry, Jae-in…
I'm sorry you had to see me like this.
Kang Pi-o.
Why'd'ya do it?
I heard everything.
I wish you would have told me sooner.
Told me it wasn't you.
You should've at least been honest with me.
I'm sorry.
You know…
even if I didn't do it,
I'd be lying if I said I never wanted to.
Even if my mom hadn't done it,
I would've wanted to get rid of you at some point, I guess.
That's what it's like to be second-best.
NEW BEGINNING STARTS HERE ESTABLISHING LAW AND ORDER
Why did you do it?
You tell me first.
You made a fool out of me.
Because it was all my fault.
Um…
I've always loved seeing you smile, ever since I was a kid.
So I wanted to do whatever it took to make you smile.
When I won the competition,
you smiled brighter than I'd ever seen you smile before.
And I thought…
"This is it."
"My mom is finally proud of me."
"She's not ashamed of me…
she's actually proud of me."
In the end, I think…
I'm the one who made you this way.
Kang Pi-o.
Don't you ever think that.
It's all my fault. It has been from the start.
People always used to look at me and laugh.
But then my precious gem came along.
I said…
"The son I gave birth to is a gift from Heaven itself."
"You can mock me all you want."
"Your jeers are nothing but envy and jealousy."
Through you I had the chance to show them all.
That's why I was so hard on you all the time.
And because you did as you were told without ever complaining,
I kept pushing you even harder to become the best.
I'm so sorry.
I only wanted to help you with your music career,
but I ended up getting in the way.
You need forget about me now.
Cut ties with me and go your own way.
Go spread your wings.
And only think about the music that you love.
You must have been sick and tired of living as my son.
Well, I'm just as sick of it.
Sick of being your mother.
Continuing from yesterday,
we'll be rehearsing the Lacrimosa from Mozart's Requiem.
As you know, this was…
the last piece of music Mozart worked on before he died.
And as though he foresaw his own death,
Mozart filled -
each and every note with a sense of foreboding.
So, the violins should,
as the name "Lacrimosa", suggests,
They should sound like teardrops falling one by one.
The chorus
should take their time and then gradually build,
like one slowly approaching the seat of judgment,
with the tension rising carefully, steadily and with conviction.
Full of tears
Will be that day
What are the details of your mother's crime?
Isa it true she hired the kidnappers?
When from the ashes
--Since when did you know about the case… -Please say a few words.
-Do you have any comment? -What will you do now?
Will you play again?
Shall arise
The guilty man
to be judged
Full of tears
Will be that day
When from the ashes
Shall arise
The guilty man
to be judged
Therefore spare him,
O God
Merciful Lord
Lord Jesus
SPECIAL APPEARANCE BY KO CHANG-SEOK
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
I can't believe such a prominent family like his could unravel so quickly?
This mean our little project's kaput now?
I'm done for good.
Everything.
It all happened because of my greed.
Come with me. I've something to show you.
The only thing we can do now, is just keep making music.
Just like that day. Freely.
Jeong-yo, uh… sent in his resignation letter, and now I can't reach him.
Just let me ask you this one favor…